我们现在是朋友了吗？
Are we friends now?
嘿 我从来没见过你 你好吗
Hey, I haven't seen you in forever. How are you?
不 我很好
No, I'm good.
天哪 他这么说？
My gosh, he said that?
我的天啊 太可爱了！
My god, that is so cute!
- 早上好！ - 你好 安吉拉阿姨
- Morning! - Hi, Aunt Angela.
- 给 让我来 我来了 - 谢谢
- Here, let me get it. I got it. - Thank you.
我看起来怎么样？我知道这才9个月 但我不知道
How do I look? I know it's only been nine months, but I don't know,
- 我觉得我好像少了一两步  - 你看起来很棒
- I feel like I lost a step or two. - You look great.
女士们早餐变冷了！
Ladies! Breakfast is getting cold!
我闻到了碳水化合物的味道 为什么他总是这样？
I smell carbs. Why does he always do this?
因为他在努力 因为我们就是这样做的 对吧？
Because he's trying. Because that's what we do, right?
我们站起来 让它发挥作用
We rise above and we make it work.
- 米阿莫尔 王子  - 来了！
- Mi amor. Princesa. - Coming!
我的意思是 以前简单多了
I mean, it was just so much simpler before.
我知道 是的 但我为你感到骄傲
I know. It was. But I'm proud of you.
我为我们感到骄傲 我是说 看看我们 我们是完整的
I'm proud of us. I mean, look at us. We're complete.
- 我们现在就像一个幸福的大家庭  - 减去碳水化合物
- We're like one big, happy family now. - Minus the carbs.
我喜欢那个
I like that one.
下面见
See you down there.
不 太可爱了
No, that's so cute.
- 你想喝杯咖啡吗？ - 是的 请
- You want a coffee? - Yes, please.
嘿 漂亮
Hey, gorgeous.
- 我爱你穿这些衣服  - 退出
- I love you in these. - Quit it.
我不能
I can't.
早上好烙饼？
Good morning! Pancakes?
今天是大日子吗？
So, big day today?
- 我们还有大约两周的时间  - 你紧张吗？
- We're still about two weeks out. - You nervous?
艾玛并不紧张 不像她的阿姨
Emma doesn't get nervous. Not like her auntie.
她有这个
She's got this.
我们今天已经完成了舞蹈的学习
We actually finish learning the dance routine today.
它很短 就像四个八点计数
It's short, like, four eight counts.
然后我们要发表演讲 向大家介绍
Then we have to make a speech, we present to everybody,
然后每个人都投票
then everyone votes,
获奖者是舞蹈队少年队长
and the winner is Dance Team Captain Junior year.
有竞争吗？
Any competition?
斯蒂芬 但是
Steph, but...
我是说 不是真的 你知道吗？
I mean, not really, you know?
我不知道 Digame
I don't know. Digame.
我有点棒
I'm kinda awesome.
- 恩español？ - 我学法语
- En español? - I take French.
Je suis géniale
Je suis géniale.
此外 你不是真正的古巴人
Besides, it's not like you're really Cuban.
大豆酱！我是说 当然 我只是一个巨大的古巴档案
Soy asombroso! I mean, sure, I'm just a huge Cuba-file,
但我身上可能有古巴血统
but there could be some Cuban blood in me somewhere.
我会在年底前让你说流利的
I'm going to get you fluent by the end of the year.
斯蒂芬的妈妈经营儿科
Steph's mom runs Pediatrics.
瑞秋和我是多年的朋友
Rachel and I have been friends for years.
好吧 祝最好的舞者获胜
Well, may the best dancer win.
试试看 它们不含麸质 零卡路里
Try them. They're gluten-free. Zero-calorie.
高蛋白
High-protein.
这么好
So good.
对
Yes!
你真有趣 米吉托！你真有趣！
You are so funny, mijito! You are so funny!
但你不能比你爸爸聪明！不 你不能
But you can't outsmart your papa! No, you cannot.
这些天他喜欢两件事
Two things he loves these days,
美味的燕麦和他的勺子
Yummy Oats and throwing his spoons.
给你
There you go.
- 嘿 你确定你没事吗？ - 好吗？你在开玩笑吧？
- Hey, you sure you're okay with this? - Okay with it? Are you kidding me?
我很幸运
I'm lucky.
我的意思是 远程课程更短了 我开始写书
I mean, remote classes are shorter, I get to work on my book,
修复野兽
fix up The Beast.
- 我讨厌野兽  - 不 你喜欢野兽
- I hate The Beast. - No, you love The Beast...
我会完善我的烹饪 最重要的是
And I get to perfect my cooking and, best of all,
我要照顾我们的儿子
I get to take care of our son.
你可以在游泳池周围设置围栏
And you get to put up a fence around the pool
在婴儿开始行走之前
before the baby starts walking.
我要在游泳池周围竖起围栏
And I get to put up a fence around the pool
在婴儿开始行走之前
before the baby starts walking.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
嘿 在我忘记之前 你们有没有看到我的露营刀？
Hey, before I forget, have either of you seen my camping knife?
你知道 那个有雕刻把手的黑色的？
You know, the black one with the carved handle?
- 我会留意的  - 谢谢 公主
- I'll keep an eye out. - Gracias, princesa.
过来
Come here.
享受 享受！吃你的煎饼
Enjoy, enjoy! Eat your pancakes.
当然
Of course.
艾玛 凯德怎么了？
Emma, what's wrong with Cade?
如果他扔了勺子 洗碗机里就会有新的
If he threw his spoon, there's some new ones in the dishwasher.
- 这是什么？ - 罗伯想和你谈谈这件事
- What's this? - Rob wanted to talk to you about that.
他过去常在那里讲课 他说这太神奇了
He used to lecture there. He said it's amazing.
95%的毕业生就读常春藤
95% of their graduates go Ivy.
- 既然我知道你在看耶鲁… - 这是寄宿学校吗？
- Since I know you're looking at Yale... - Is it a boarding school?
不 不 不是那样 离这里只有几个小时的路程
No, no. Not like that. It's only a couple hours away,
这样你周末就可以回家了
so you could come home on the weekends.
等一下！
Just a second!
- 这是罗伯的主意？ - 他只想要对你最好的东西
- This was Rob's idea? - He just wants what's best for you.
无论如何 这只是需要考虑的事情
Anyways, it's just something to think about.
- 祝你今天好运 玩得开心  - 谢谢 孩子 我需要这个
- Good luck today. Have fun. - Thanks, kiddo. I needed that.
- 斯蒂芬 你看起来真可爱  - 真正地
- Steph, you look so cute. - Really?
我一直在告诉你 这是装饰品 对吧 Em？
I keep telling you. It's adorbs. Right, Em?
- 是的 它真的很适合你  - 你不觉得太短吗？
- Yeah. It really suits you. - You don't think it's too short?
不你在开玩笑吧？你看起来很棒
No! Are you kidding me? You look amazing.
- 看起来很棒  - 非常感谢
- It looks great. - Thank you.
好吧第二定律
All right. Second Law.
斯蒂芬妮？
Stephanie?
物体动量随时间的变化率
The rate of change of momentum of a body over time
与…成正比
is directly proportional to...
谁能帮她？艾玛！把生意交给我们！
Who can help her out? Emma! Give us the business!
物体动量随时间的变化率
The rate of change of momentum of a body over time
与所施加的力成正比
is directly proportional to the force applied,
并且以相同的方向发生
and occurs in the same direction.
就在那里！
And there it is!
现在 为了所有的弹珠
And now, for all the marbles.
牛顿的
What is Newton's...
- 对不起  - 进来吧 别害羞
- Sorry. - Come on in. Don't be shy.
物理是最适合的地方！
Physics is the place to be!
- 好了 各位 这是凯瑟琳… - 凯特
- Okay, everyone, this is Katherine... - Kat.
只有凯特
Just Kat.
凯特·桑德伯格 她是从北部调来的
Kat Sandberg. She's a transfer from upstate.
我相信你们都会让她感到受欢迎
I'm sure you'll all make her feel welcome.
那边有个地方
There's a spot just over there.
好吧回到Big Kahuna
All right. Back to the Big Kahuna.
牛顿第三运动定律？任何人
Newton's Third Law of Motion? Anyone?
让我眼花缭乱 格罗斯曼
Dazzle me, Grossman.
每一个动作都有一个相等和相反的反应
Every action has an equal and opposite reaction.
第44页
Page 44.
你好他们把你移到我旁边
Hello! They moved you next to me.
我知道 我很幸运
I know. Lucky me.
好吧 那就把这看作是乔迁之喜吧
Well, consider this a housewarming then.
- 还是你的最爱 对吧？ - 你记得了
- Still your favorite, right? - You remembered.
把它们藏在桌子下面 这样居民就不会偷了
Hide them under the desk so the residents don't steal them.
天哪！他不就是一切吗？
My gosh! Isn't he just everything?
- 看看那头发！ - 我知道
- Look at that hair! - I know.
- 你还好吗？ - 好的
- How're you holding up? - Fine.
不知怎么的 我有12000封未读邮件
I somehow have 12,000 unread emails.
- 这怎么可能？ - 我知道
- How is that even possible? - I know.
嘿 听着 你有时间吗？我想让你做点什么
Hey, listen, you got a second? I want to run something by you.
- 是的 当然  - 舞蹈队队长试镜
- Yeah. Of course. - Dance Team Captain auditions.
你也是 对吧？
You too, right?
艾玛一直在倒数 它是
Emma has been counting down the days. It is...
- 荒谬  - 是 啊
- Ridiculous. - Yeah.
女孩在这个年龄段已经很缺乏安全感和竞争力
Girls are already so insecure and so competitive at this age.
你知道斯蒂芬这个周末理发后哭了多久吗？
You know how long Steph cried after she got her hair cut this weekend?
所以我在想   睡衣派对 披萨 愚蠢的游戏
So I was thinking... slumber party. Pizza, goofy games.
好的 干净的乐趣只是为了减轻压力
Good, clean fun to just lighten it up, take the pressure off.
艾玛会喜欢的
Emma would love that.
格罗斯曼医生到急诊室3
Dr. Grossman to Emergency Room 3.
他们知道你在这里
They know you're here.
最好进去 医生 这就像骑自行车一样
Better get in there, doc. It's just like riding a bike.
可以
Okay...
好的 让我们再次从最后一节开始 艾玛 跳进去
Okay, let's take it from that last section again. Emma, jump in.
和
And...
五 六 七 八！
five, six, seven, eight!
停止你太僵硬了
Stop. You're too stiff.
松软的脚让我偏头痛
Floppy feet give me migraines.
还有脸！给我面子！
And face! Give me face!
那真是一团糟 好的 再来一次
That was a hot mess. Okay, one more time.
斯蒂芬 加入艾玛
Steph, jump in for Emma.
艾玛 我们需要你多练习
Emma, we need more practice from you.
和五 六 七 八！
And... five, six, seven, eight!
艾米 注意你的间距
Amy, watch your spacing.
还有脸！
And face!
较好的好了 姑娘们 屏住呼吸
Better. Okay, girls, catch your breath.
干得好 斯蒂芬妮
Great job, Stephanie.
- 再见 伙计们  - 再见
- Bye, guys. - See ya.
艾玛 你来吗？
Emma, you coming?
- 我需要几分钟  - 别担心 你会得到的
- I need a few minutes. - Don't worry, you'll get it.
艾玛！
Emma!
- 怎么了？ - 嘿 内森
- What's up? - Hey, Nathan.
需要搭车吗？
Need a ride?
我就在拐角处
I'm right around the corner.
可以好的 很酷
Okay. Okay, cool.
那么下次呢？
Next time then?
- 当然  - 可以
- Sure. - Okay.
- 稍后  - 再见
- Later. - Bye.
好了 伙计们 欢迎回来
All right, guys, welcome back.
我想确保这次你们都带上相机 没有猫表情符号
I want to make sure you all have your cameras on and no cat emoticons this time
因为上次我们
because last time, we...
嘴巴在动 是的 所以 确保你的相机打开
The mouth was moving, yeah. So, make sure your cameras are on.
特雷弗 你的相机打开了 我不想看不到你的脸 好吗？
Trevor, your camera is on. I don't like to not see your face, okay?
所以我们开始了
So here we go.
这是我向大家提出的问题
This is the question that I pose to all of you.
在我们研究过的所有小说中
Which author, of all the novels that we've studied,
最能代表古巴的心脏和灵魂？
best represents the heart and soul of Cuba?
阿里纳斯？
Arenas?
步兵？木匠？
Infante? Carpentier?
你们中的一些人甚至会为帕杜拉辩护
Some of you are even going to make an argument for Padura
我很乐意阅读
that I would be happy to read.
我只是觉得如果你回去复习第五章卡彭蒂埃
I just think that if you go back and review chapter five Carpentier,
你会发现
you're going to find...
凯德！罗伯特！我的天
Cade! Robert! My god.
- 凯德！ - 你怎么了？
- Cade! - What is the matter with you?
- 你本该看着他的！ - 我在看着他！
- You were supposed to be watching him! - I was watching him!
我不知道发生了什么！门关上了！
I don't know what happened! The door was closed!
不 它没有关闭！你知道刚才可能发生了什么吗？
No, it was not closed! Do you realize what could have just happened?
好吧 让我们冷静下来 你没事吧 伙计？
Okay, let's just calm down. Are you okay, buddy?
不 不 不！我不会冷静下来的！
No, no, no! I'm not going to calm down!
这就是为什么我想在游泳池周围设置围栏！
This is why I wanted a fence around the pool!
这正是我害怕的！
This is exactly what I was afraid of!
听着 孩子们掉进家庭游泳池后 总是会来我的急诊室
Look, kids come into my ER all the time after falling into the family pool,
拯救他们总是太晚了！你明白吗？
and it is always, always too late to save them! Do you understand?
听着 我很抱歉 好吗？我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
对不起 伙计 我很抱歉 让我们
I'm sorry, buddy. I'm so sorry. Let's just...
我要在这个游泳池周围竖起一道栅栏 让我们都呼吸一下
I'm going to get a fence put up around this pool, and let's all just breathe.
- 只是不要  - 安吉拉
- Just don't. - Angela.
这看起来很好吃
This looks delicious.
非常感谢
Thank you.
希望我们能好好吃顿饭
Hopefully, we can just have a nice dinner
忘记我之前犯的错误
and forget about the mistake that I made earlier.
太好了
That's nice.
- 这是什么？ - 我很抱歉
- What is this? - I'm so sorry.
我不知道发生了什么 这真的很咸
I don't know what happened. This is really salty.
艾玛 别吃那个
Emma, don't eat that.
我可以点中文吗？
Can I order Chinese?
当然
Sure.
- 他很喜欢你  - 我不感兴趣
- He so likes you. - I'm so not interested.
但我把你的电话号码给了他！
But I so gave him your phone number!
我感觉很糟糕
I feel bad.
我们应该邀请她和我们一起坐吗？
Should we, like, invite her to sit with us or whatever?
- 你太好了 斯蒂芬  - 我会做的
- You're too nice, Steph. - I'll do it.
你好我是艾玛
Hi! I'm Emma.
我知道
I know.
那些是我的朋友 斯蒂芬和萝拉
Those are my friends. Steph and Lola.
我们跳舞
We dance.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
如果你愿意 你可以和我们坐在一起
If you want, you can, like, sit with us.
不 谢谢
No thanks.
认真地
Seriously?
你不认识我 是吗？
You don't recognize me, do you?
我应该吗？
Should I?
再见 艾玛
Bye, Emma.
好吧 如果你觉得无聊或其他什么的话 这个提议仍然有效
Well, the offer still stands if you get bored or whatever.
只有愚蠢的人才会感到无聊
Only stupid people get bored.
- 嗯？ - 她说“也许以后再说 ”
- Well? - She said "maybe later."
嘿 艾玛 你能进来一下吗？
Hey, Emma. Can you come in here for a minute?
是 啊怎么了？
Yeah. What's up?
罗伯特和我有个惊人的消息
Robert and I have some amazing news.
你想告诉她还是想让我告诉她？
Did you want to tell her or do you want me to tell her?
不 你告诉她 告诉她
No, you tell her, you tell her.
罗伯特帮了你几个忙 让你被圣克里斯平医院录取了
Robert called in a few favors, got you accepted to St. Crispin's
大三和大四！
for your Junior and Senior year!
不过我在这里做得很好
I'm doing so well here, though.
好吧 那你可能会在那里做得很好
Well, then you'll probably do really good there.
这不是很好吗？
Isn't that great?
是 啊这太不可思议了
Yeah. This is incredible.
- 谢谢你 罗伯特  - 不客气
- Thank you, Robert. - You're welcome.
嘿 我找到了我的刀
And, hey, I found my knife.
好吧 好消息到处都是
Well, good news all around.
我们应该庆祝一下 明天我做些牛排怎么样？
We should celebrate. How about tomorrow I make some steak?
- 是的 请！那太棒了  - 听起来很棒 等不及了
- Yes, please! That would be awesome. - Sounds great. Can't wait.
是的 我中午可以和你见面
Yeah, I can meet you at noon.
不 那是我能最早到达的地方 我十点钟有两个约会
No, that's the earliest I can be there. I have two appointments at ten.
我知道 是 啊可以
I know. Yeah. Okay.
请告诉我确切的位置
Just let me know exactly where...
- 你想要什么？ - 我想你知道
- What do you want? - I think you know.
你知道电椅上发生了什么吗？
Do you know what happens in the electric chair?
艾玛！
Emma!
它把你烤熟了
It cooks you.
你的皮肤像早上自制的培根一样干裂干瘪
Your skin crackles and shrivels like homemade bacon in the morning.
没事的 爸爸 我从来不会无缘无故地伤害任何人
It's okay, Daddy. I'd never hurt anyone for no reason.
一篮子吻
A basket of kisses.
A basket of kisses...
- 嗯？艾玛 怎么了？ - 没有什么只是累了
- Em? Emma, what's wrong? - Nothing. Just tired.
- 苏普？我能加入你们吗？ - 是的 绝对
- S'up? Can I join you guys? - Yeah, absolutely.
- 到目前为止 你觉得这里怎么样？ - 我哪里都不喜欢
- So, how do you like it here so far? - I don't like it anywhere.
- 你不能在这里抽烟  - 不
- You can't smoke in here. - No?
- 那你是从哪里转过来的？ - 圣奥尔登酒店
- So where'd you transfer from? - St. Alden's.
我的上帝！所以你们两个认识吗？
My God! So you two, like, know each other?
伊什 我当时叫凯蒂
Ish. I went by Katie back then.
你应该说点什么
You should've said something.
你觉得你很聪明 你最终会明白的
You think you're smart. You would've figured it out eventually.
- 或者不是  - 所以等等
- Or not. - So wait.
你认识那个溺水的孩子吗？
You knew that kid who drowned?
- 那个老师呢？ - 是 啊
- And that teacher? - Yeah.
对不起你爸爸的事
Sorry about your dad.
没事的
It's fine.
- 我想… - 你应该问问她
- I think... - You should ask her.
我明天要在我家开一个睡衣派对
I'm having a slumber party at my place tomorrow.
这更像是一个舞蹈队的事情 但你完全应该来
It's more of a dance team thing, but you should totally come.
大概
Maybe.
再见 艾玛
See ya around, Emma.
听起来不错
That sounds good.
和这是给你的
And... this is for you.
非常感谢
Thank you.
德纳达
De nada.
- 你知道吗… - 这听起来像是大便般的叫声
- You know what... - That sounds like a poopy cry.
- 放开我！ - 不 我明白了 让我
- Let me go! - No. I got it. Let me just...
- 你确定吗？ - 这样做
- Are you sure? - do this.
- 你能看这个吗？ - 我会看的
- Can you watch this? - I will watch this.
- 我马上回来  - 我会尽力的
- I'll be right back. - I'll do my best.
- 那是你的手机吗？ - 该死 在办公室里
- Is that your phone? - Darn it. It's in the office.
可以你看这些 我两分钟
Okay... you watch these, I'll be two minutes.
可以
Okay.
你好
Hello?
嘿 是的 我们肯定还有十分钟
Hey, yes. We're definitely still on for ten.
好的 一切都干净
Okay, all clean.
一切都很干净 好孩子
All clean. Good boy.
罗伯特？
Robert?
来吧
Come on!
罗伯特！
Robert!
灭火器   它在水槽下面！
The fire extinguisher... it's under the sink!
艾玛 不 不要
Emma, no, don't.
我以为你应该在看
I thought you were supposed to be watching it.
我在看 我不知道发生了什么 我把它留给艾玛了
I was watching it. I don't know what happened. I left it with Emma.
我不得不去洗手间 我离开了两秒钟
I had to go to the bathroom. I was gone for two seconds.
- 这不是我的错！ - 那是谁的错？
- It's not my fault! - Well, then whose fault is it?
好的 请安静 你们两个
Okay, quiet, please, both of you.
- 我们应该再做一次外卖吗？ - 外卖很好
- Should we do takeout again? - Takeout's fine.
你知道 无论你说话与否 成本都是一样的
You know, it costs the same whether you talk or not.
我知道
I'm aware.
你的脑子里到底在想什么？
What is running through that brain of yours?
如果物理定律也适用于人呢？
What if the laws of physics applied to people as well?
行动相等和相反的反应？
Action. Equal and opposite reaction?
我认为这不是牛顿的意思
I don't think that's what Newton meant.
我阿姨想送我去寄宿学校
My aunt wants to send me to a boarding school.
我知道 为了记录在案 我听说学校很优秀
I'm aware. And just for the record, I've heard that school is outstanding.
- 它的校友最终在全国各地的常春藤盟校毕业
- Its alumni end up at... - Ivy Leagues all across the country.
我知道 我已经看过小册子了 两次
I'm aware. I've read the brochure. Twice.
大多数穿你鞋子的女孩都会很兴奋
Most girls in your shoes would be thrilled.
- 罗伯特要我离开房子  - 他为什么要这样？
- Robert wants me out of the house. - And why would he want that?
你的行为是否会促使他做出决定？
Did you behave in such a way that might have precipitated his decision?
你的行为引起了反应吗？
Did your action cause a reaction?
- 也许吧  - 所以你制造了一个问题
- Maybe. - So you created a problem.
对于我们自己制造的问题 正确的反应是什么？
And what is the proper response to a problem of our own making?
解决问题
Solving it.
你擅长解决问题 是吗？
And you are good at solving problems, aren't you?
对我很擅长解决问题
Yes. I'm very good at solving problems.
谢谢你 马奇博士 这非常有帮助
Thank you, Dr. March. This has been incredibly helpful.
我很高兴能够帮助你 艾玛
I am so glad to have been able to help you, Emma.
好吧再见
All right. Bye.
罗伯特 我想道歉
Robert, I wanted to apologize...
罗伯特叔叔 我只是想道歉
Uncle Robert, I just wanted to apologize...
你好
Hi.
- 嘿  - 我以为你可能渴了
- Hey. - I thought you might be thirsty.
我们能谈谈吗？
Can we talk?
罗伯特叔叔 我只是想道歉
Uncle Robert, I just wanted to apologize
因为忘了把刀还给你
for forgetting to give you back your knife.
我在所有泳池设备旁边找到了它
I found it next to all the pool equipment
我忘了把它还给你 所以
and it just slipped my mind to give it back to you, so...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
非常感谢
Thank you.
你知道 每个人都很难改变
You know, change is hard for everyone.
对我来说 在我爸爸之后
For me, after my dad, you know,
只是   我想 有时候 我脑子里有东西
it's just... I guess, sometimes, something gets in my head and...
也许我会做一些我不该做的事
maybe I'll do something I shouldn't have.
我理解
I understand.
也许这对我们有好处？也许我们可以重新开始
Maybe this is good for us? Maybe we could start over.
是 啊
Yeah.
谁知道呢 也许圣克里斯平对我有好处
And who knows, maybe St. Crispin's will be good for me.
- 真的吗？ - 是 啊90%的毕业生就读常春藤
- Really? - Yeah. 90% of their grads go Ivy.
我想去常春藤 所以我想说这很有可能
I want to go Ivy, so I'd say those are pretty good odds.
是 啊
Yeah.
此外 你在做对你的家人和我最有利的事 所以
Besides, you're doing what's best for your family and for me, so.
非常感谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
过来
Come here.
艾玛 你想搭车去派对吗？
Emma, do you want a ride to the party?
不 斯蒂芬斯就在拐角处 我要走了
No, Steph's is right around the corner. I'm going to walk.
可以好吧 玩得开心！如果你需要什么 请告诉我 什么都可以
Okay. Well, have fun! Just let me know if you need anything. Anything at all.
- 我会的  - 和
- I will. - And...
罗伯特告诉我你们俩很好
Robert told me you two are good.
你不知道这让我有多开心 亲爱的熊
You have no idea how happy that makes me, honey bear.
艾玛？
Emma?
安吉拉？
Angela?
进来吧
Come in!
- 嗨！ - 你好
- Hi! - Hi.
来吧 请坐
Come on. Go have a seat.
- 这不是很好笑吗？ - 真是太搞笑了
- Isn't that hilarious? - That's so hilarious.
你们得到了什么？
What did you guys get?
- 我想是的 - 我就是这么说的
- I think so. - That's what I said.
那是谁？
Who's that?
- 是凯特 - 对
- It's Kat. - Right.
我还是不明白你们为什么要邀请她
I still don't see why you guys had to invite her.
因为她是你的朋友 我想表现得很好
Because she's your friend. I was trying to be nice.
很高兴有一些女孩在这里
It is so nice to have some of the girls on the team here.
现在 你们女孩玩得很开心 记住
Now, you girls have fun. And remember,
你真正与之竞争的人只有你自己
the only person you're ever really competing with is yourself.
- 谢谢 妈妈  - 这真的很有帮助
- Thanks, Mom. - That's really helpful.
你和艾玛以前认识有多酷？
So how cool is it that you and Emma used to know each other?
不过 我们并不是真正的朋友
We weren't really friends, though.
我们没有？
We weren't?
我是说 让我们面对现实吧 你和任何人都不是真正的朋友
I mean, let's face it. You weren't really friends with anyone.
- 我肯定那不是真的  - 确实如此
- I'm sure that's not true. - It so is.
还记得那次我绊倒了 你偷了我的手表吗？
Remember that time I tripped and you stole my watch?
- 我不认为那是我
- I don't think that was me. - It was.
但不管怎样 很酷
But whatever. It's cool.
有人想玩游戏吗？
Anyone wanna play a game?
对
Yes.
罗伯特？
Robert?
可以既然这是我的房子 我能先走吗？
Okay. Do I get to go first since it's my house?
我从来没有在考试中作弊过
Never have I ever cheated on a test.
我的天 我的天
My god. My god.
我很高兴我们在加油站上了老学校
Love that we are goin' old school on the gas.
可以
Okay...
我从来没有在汽车的前排座位上亲热过
Never have I ever made out in the front seat of a car.
B.S.公司
B.S.
我没有说任何关于背部的事
I didn't say anything about the back.
我的上帝 圣艾玛 你什么都没做过
My god, Saint Emma. You've never done anything.
我甚至在吃药 还在抽烟
I'm even on meds and I'm smoking.
- 下一个是谁？ - 我要走了
- Who's next? - I'll go.
让它变好
Make it good.
我从来没有   杀死了任何人
Never have I ever... killed anyone.
你是谁   你杀了谁？
Who did you... Who did you kill?
- 我妈妈 当我出生时  - 感谢上帝
- My mom. When I born. - Thank God.
- 你知道我的意思  - 你以为我是什么意思？
- You know what I mean. - What'd you think I meant?
你以为我真的杀了人吗？我不是疯子
Did you think I actually killed someone? I'm not a psycho.
- 什么… - 妈妈
- What the... - Mom!
艾玛 亲爱的 拿好你的东西 我带你去医院
Emma, honey, grab your things. I'm taking you to the hospital.
- 为什么？ - 发生了一起事故 来吧
- Why? - There's been an accident. Come on.
我们稍后再讨论
We will talk about this later.
- 安吉拉阿姨？ - 艾玛 过来
- Aunt Angela? - Emma. Come here.
- 发生了什么？ - 他被钉住了
- What happened? - He was pinned...
那辆车 我一直讨厌那辆车
That car. I've always hated that car, and the...
千斤顶不知怎么出了故障
the jack malfunctioned somehow,
他被钉在下面 天知道有多久了
and he was pinned under it for god knows how long.
但他很强壮 他一直很坚强
But he's strong. He's always been strong.
所以现在我们只能拭目以待了
And so now we just have to wait and see.
我们现在是朋友了吗？
Are we friends now?
你真傻
You're silly.
我知道你现在不想吃东西
I know you don't want to eat right now.
保持体力很重要
It's important to keep your strength up.
这就是罗伯特希望你做的
That's what Robert would want you to do.
- 凯德？ - 他很好
- Cade? - He's fine.
把他放下来睡午觉
Just put him down for his nap.
小家伙甚至不知道有什么问题
Little guy doesn't even know anything's wrong.
杂货店一小时后就要来了
Groceries are coming in an hour.
没有你我该怎么办 亲爱的熊？
What would I do without you, honey bear?
他会没事吗？
Is he going to be okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们会挺过去的 好吗？
We're going to make it through this, all right?
因为我们是格罗斯曼 这就是我们所做的
Because we're Grossmans. That's what we do.
- 我们站起来 让它发挥作用  - 这是正确的
- We rise above and we make it work. - That's right.
是 啊
Yeah.
- 喂？这是艾玛  - 嘿 艾玛 我是内森
- Hello? This is Emma. - Hey, Emma. It's Nathan.
你好
Hi.
斯蒂芬告诉我你叔叔的事 我只是
Steph told me about your uncle and I just...
我只是想登记一下 看看你过得怎么样
I just wanted to check in, see how you were holding up.
- 是的 我   我很好  - 可以酷 酷
- Yeah, I'm... I'm fine. - Okay. Cool, cool.
我只是在检查
I was just checking.
可以
Okay.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?
罗伯特 罗伯特！
Robert, Robert!
不 不 你现在得把它留着 没关系
No. No, you've got to leave that in for now. It's okay.
如果你能听到我的话就点头
Nod if you can hear me.
这很好 你知道你在哪里吗？
That's good. Do you know where you are?
你在医院里 发生了意外 你受伤了
You're in a hospital. There was an accident and you got hurt.
我们只需要把你拔下管子 然后送你回家
We just have to get you extubated and get you home,
通过理疗 几个月后你就能起床走路了
and with physio therapy, you're going to be up and walking in a few months.
没关系 没关系 请不要   不要动
It's okay, it's okay. Please, don't... don't move.
罗伯特 你还记得发生了什么吗？
Robert, do you remember what happened?
你想写点什么吗？
You want to write something?
可以是 啊
Okay. Yeah.
在这里
Here.
给你 给你
There you go. There you go.
过去几年来我一直和你们跳舞 我只是
I've been dancing with you girls for the past couple of years now. I just...
我不知道 我们在一起玩得很开心
I don't know, we've had so much fun together.
我们在一起玩得很开心
We've had so much fun together.
- 我们   我们已经… - 艾玛？你能下楼吗？
- We've... we've had... - Emma? Can you come downstairs?
来了！
Coming!
- 你很早就回家了  - 我有一个令人难以置信的消息
- You're home early. - I have incredible news.
- 什么？ - 罗伯特会挺过来的
- What? - Robert's going to pull through.
- 我知道他会成功的  - 是 啊
- I knew he'd make it through. - Yeah.
我不想让他在那里呆得太久
I don't want to keep him in there a minute longer than he has to be,
所以我们要把他安置在这里 我要请一名护士
so we're going to set him up down here, I'm bringing in a nurse,
物理治疗师
physical therapist.
在我们知道之前 他会站起来走路
He's going to be up and walking before we know it.
他说什么了吗？
Has he said anything?
他有闪光
He's had flashes.
什么样的闪光？
What kind of flashes?
没有什么具体的 就是这样
Nothing specific. That's it.
我记得发生在我身上的一切
I remember everything that happened to me.
- 是的 但你很特别 艾玛  - 我知道
- Yeah, but you're special, Emma. - I know.
你是他来的第一个被问到的人
And you're the first person he asked about when he came to.
- 他说了什么？ - 他问你是否没事
- What did he say? - He asked if you were all right.
他爱你 亲爱的
He loves you, honeybear.
我需要去练习 明天是选举
I need to go and practice. Election's tomorrow.
玩得高兴
Have fun.
发生什么事？
What's going on?
- 你没听说吗？ - 不
- You haven't heard? - No.
我的地方一直很忙
Things have been kinda busy at my place.
- 斯蒂芬在哪里？ - 不来了
- Where's Steph? - Not coming.
为什么？
Why?
昨晚有人从她家后院偷走了她的狗
Somebody totally stole her dog out of her backyard last night,
今天早上 一些慢跑者发现了它
and this morning, some jogger found it.
- 还有？ - 它死了 艾玛！
- And? - It was dead, Emma!
就像 被切碎 被刺伤 到处都是血和内脏！
Like, chopped up and stabbed, and blood and guts everywhere!
那真是一部恐怖电影
That is so horror movie.
- 他们知道是谁干的吗？ - 一些精神病患者
- Do they know who did it? - Some psychopath.
全世界都是他们 这就是为什么有这么多播客
The world is full of them. That's why there's so many podcasts.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 内森
Hey, Nathan.
- 怎么了？ - 不多
- What's up? - Not much.
- 我能送你去上课吗？ - 当然
- Can I walk you to class? - Sure.
好的 女士们 安顿下来
Okay, ladies. Settle in.
我们现在有点进退两难
We have a bit of a dilemma before us at the moment.
斯蒂芬妮·洛福德
Stephanie Lowford.
显然 她不是来试镜的 而且是有充分理由的
She's not here to audition, obviously, and for good reason.
所以 问题是她明年是否仍有资格成为队长？
So, the question becomes is she still eligible for Captain next year?
我答应了 我的意思是 有人在她的小狗身上捅了一刀 这不是她的错
I say yes. I mean, it's not her fault someone went all stabby-stab on her pup.
她真的很想这样 而且她一直非常努力
She really wants this and she's been working super hard.
有人反对吗？
Any opposed?
艾玛
Emma.
我只是想说我同意萝拉的观点
I just wanted to say that I agree with Lola.
我想我们都知道
I think that we all do.
女孩？
Girls?
可以那我们就开始吧
Okay. Then let's get to it.
还有兴趣竞选队长的人过来
Anyone still interested in running for Captain, come up here
告诉我们为什么你认为你是最好的领导团队
and tell us why you think you'd be the best to lead the team.
然后 我们将进行无记名投票
Then afterwards, we're going to vote by secret ballot,
是的 你仍然可以投票给斯蒂芬妮
and, yes, you can still vote for Stephanie.
那么 谁是第一个？
So, who's first?
地板是你的
The floor is yours.
过去几年我一直和你们跳舞
I've been dancing with you girls for the past couple years now,
我只是觉得我们在一起很开心
and I just feel like we have so much fun together.
我只是想确保我们在一起留下美好的回忆
I just really want to make sure that we make good memories together,
因为我想能够回顾他们
because I want to be able to look back on them
我想 当我们都老了 头发花白了 可以说
when we're all old and gray, I guess, and be able to say...
“该死 舞蹈队真的病了 ”
"Damn, dance team was really sick."
我只是
And I just...
你知道的
You know...
就像我说的 我只是真的想要
Like I said, I just really want
继续和你们一起创造美好的回忆
to keep on making great memories with you guys.
我爱你们 而且
I love you all, and...
我不知道 我想这是我的“演讲”
I don't know, I guess that's my "speech".
请投票给我当舞蹈队长
Please vote for me as dance captain.
如果你不这么做 我想
If you don't, no hard feelings, I guess,
是的 走吧 黄蜂！
and, yeah, go, Wasps!
好了 下一个是谁？
Okay, who's up next?
嘿
Hey.
好消息 罗伯特一周后就能回家
Good news. Robert gets to come home in one week.
我只需要为他整理一下这个房间
I just have to sort out this room for him.
- 因为他的轮椅  - 太好了
- Because of his wheelchair. - That's great.
这个周末你将接受圣克里斯平的采访
And you have an interview with St. Crispin's this weekend.
他们只是想和你打交道
They just want to touch base with you
看看你对入学的感觉 好吗？
and see how you're feeling about enrollment, okay?
我等不及了
I can't wait.
进展如何？
How did it go?
斯蒂芬赢了 我真为她高兴
Steph won. I am so happy for her.
- 艾玛 你想谈谈吗？ - 不 不 我没有 很抱歉打扰一下
- Emma, do you want to talk about it? - No. No, I don't. Sorry. Excuse me.
艾玛
Emma.
就在这里
Right here.
别担心 我有多年的经验
Don't you worry, I've got many years' experience.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
这里很好 杰出的
That's good here. Excellent.
因为家里有一个青少年
Since there is a teen in the household,
药柜必须始终上锁
the medicine cabinet must remain locked at all times.
随身携带一把钥匙 随身携带 我也会随身携带
Take one key and keep it on your person, always, and I'll have mine as well.
可以
Okay.
艾玛 嘿
Emma. Hey.
进来 公主 不要害羞
Come in, princesa. Don't be shy.
我侄女艾玛 艾玛 这是科拉
My niece, Emma. Emma, this is Cora.
她将在白天和我们一起帮助罗伯特
She's going to be with us during the day to help out with Robert.
- 嗨  - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
如果你需要什么 请告诉我
If you ever need anything, just let me know.
我在考虑像我阿姨一样去医学院
I'm thinking about going into medicine like my aunt.
杰出的你应该如此骄傲
Excellent. You should be so proud.
你好
Hi.
很高兴你回到家里
It's nice to have you back inside the house.
回家真好
It's so good to be home.
你感觉怎么样？
How do you feel?
非常非常糟糕
Very, very bad.
20分钟后服用止痛药
Pain meds in 20 minutes.
我现在很痛苦
I'm in so much pain right now.
是的 重点是让你被淘汰 而不是让你上钩
Yeah, the point is to get you weened off, not get you hooked.
正确的你能告诉我我的臀部和腿吗？
Right. Can you tell that to my hips and my legs?
- 罗伯特… - 我很好
- Robert... - I'm fine.
你还记得发生了什么吗？
Do you remember what happened?
不
No.
纳达 只是
Nada. Just...
黑色
black.
- 卫生间？ - 是 啊让我给你看
- Restroom? - Yeah. Let me show you.
你渴吗？
Are you thirsty?
在这里
Here.
什么
What?
没有什么
Nothing.
我给你带来了这个
I brought you this.
这样 你总能感觉到他很亲近
That way, you can always feel close to him.
真周到 艾玛 非常感谢
That's very thoughtful, Emma. Thank you.
我在努力坚持下去 就像我能坚持多久一样
I'm trying to stick at it, like, as long as I can.
- 你能给我们一秒钟吗？ - 是的 当然 绝对地
- Think you could give us a second? - Yeah, sure. Absolutely.
- 我会在课堂上和你见面  - 可以再见
- I'll just meet you in class. - Okay. Bye.
- 什么？你想要什么？ - 那就是现在的情况？六
- What? What do you want? - So that's what now? Six?
- 六个什么？ - 六个不幸的巧合
- Six what? - Six unfortunate coincidences.
但最后一个并没有按照你想要的方式进行 是吗？
But the last one didn't really work out the way you wanted it to, did it?
斯蒂芬还是打败了你 我知道你的一切
Steph still beat you. I know all about you.
- 告诉我  - 我应该从哪里开始？
- Do tell. - Where should I start?
管家从楼梯上摔下来？米洛溺水了？
With the housekeeper falling down the stairs? Milo drowning?
埃利斯太太的车祸？一个保姆被烧死？
Mrs. Ellis' car wreck? A babysitter burning to death?
一个父亲中枪了 一个继父被汽车碾压
A dad getting shot. A stepuncle getting crushed by a car.
现在一只狗在公园里被砍了？
And now a dog getting chopped up in a park?
- 巧合？还是模式？ - Stray Kat有爪子
- Coincidences? Or a pattern? - Stray Kat has claws.
你一直很忙
You've been busy.
如果我真的那么忙 你可能需要小心
If I've really been that busy, you might want to be careful.
还是怎样
Or what?
- 我会告诉大家的  - 告诉他们什么？
- I'll tell everyone. - Tell them what?
真相！
The truth!
艾玛？
Emma?
- 你要来吗？ - 我马上就到
- Are you coming? - I'll be there in a second.
事故总是发生在人们身上
Accidents happen all the time to people.
尤其是像你这样的人
Especially people like you.
像我这样的人？
People like me?
伤害自己的人
People who hurt themselves.
我可能伤害了自己 但我真的为你感到难过
I may have hurt myself, but it's really you I feel sorry for.
嗯 你不应该担心我 笨蛋
Well, you shouldn't worry about me, silly.
我为你感到难过
I feel bad for you.
你将永远孤独
You'll always be alone.
大概
Maybe.
但至少我不会是你 凯蒂凯特
But at least I won't be you, Kitty Kat.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
你不能只是打人 你到底怎么了？你没事吧？
You can't just slap people. What the hell's wrong with you? You okay?
她疯了！
She's insane!
- 这是怎么回事！ - 她扇了她一巴掌
- What's going on here! - She slapped her.
- 她扇了我一巴掌！ - 没有什么
- She slapped me! - Nothing.
凯特 那是拘留
Kat. That's detention.
滚开！
Piss off!
- 一个星期！ - 无论什么
- For a week! - Whatever!
我勒个去？
What the hell?
内森 请带她去护士办公室
Nathan, please take her to the nurse's office.
当然来吧
Of course. Come on.
你为什么不在剩下的时间里放松一下？
Why don't you just relax for the rest of the period?
如果你需要什么 请告诉我
Let me know if you need anything.
- 嘿 是什么 蜜熊？ - 没有什么
- Hey. What is it, honeybear? - Nothing.
艾玛 来吧
Emma, come on.
是我
It's me.
好吧 我明白了 这是一个艰难的几个星期 但
All right, I get it, it's been a rough couple of weeks, but...
我是说 学校怎么样？
I mean, how's school?
- 没事的  - 可以
- It's okay. - Okay?
有个女孩 她的名字是凯特
There's this girl. Her name is Kat.
她从圣奥尔登转学
She transferred from St. Alden's.
你认识她吗？她和你同年级吗？
Did you know her? Was she in the same grade as you?
不是真的
Not really.
她最近刚刚对我说了一些非常糟糕的话
She's just been saying some really awful things to me lately.
关于
About?
关于米洛
About Milo.
埃利斯夫人 我爸爸
Mrs. Ellis. My dad.
你知道 她认为我和这事有关系
You know, she thinks I had something to do with it,
发生在我们身上的一切
everything that happened to us.
我什么都不想说 但她今天打了我
I wasn't going to say anything, but she hit me today.
什么
What?
是的 最近发生的一切
Yeah, and just with everything that's been going on lately,
我是说 这太可怕了
I mean, it's just awful.
我向你保证 我会很快就把这件事搞定 可以
I promise you, I am going to squash this real quick. Okay?
我早上第一件事就是打电话
I'm going to make a phone call first thing in the morning.
过来 没关系
Come here. It's okay.
这只是一个粗糙的补丁 孩子
This is just a rough patch, kiddo.
我们会挺过去的 我保证
We are going to get through this. I promise.
嘿 没关系
Hey, it's okay.
所以有   有什么好消息吗？
So is there... any good news?
- 我是说 有个男孩… - 真正地
- I mean, there's this boy... - Really?
他很可爱
He's cute.
很抱歉
Sorry.
不 我不想听你调查
No. I don't want to hear that you'll look into it.
我希望它立即得到处理
I want it taken care of immediately.
对如果你不打算给凯特的父母打电话 我会的
Yes. And if you don't plan on calling Kat's parents, then I will.
可以好吧 非常感谢
Okay. All right then. Thank you.
- 还有好消息吗？ - 我希望如此
- More good news, I take it? - I wish.
斯蒂芬怎么样？
How's Steph?
她好了一点 因为震动已经过去了
She a bit better, now that the shock has worn off.
哈罗德答应今年夏天给她买一只新狗
Harold promised to buy her a new dog this summer.
他们还没弄清楚是谁干的？
They still haven't figured out who did this?
不 不 一个慢跑者看到有人在遛狗
No. No. A jogger saw someone walking the dog.
我们的安全摄像头上有一点 但没有确定
We got a little on our security cam, but nothing determinate.
谁做那样的事？
Who does something like that?
谁会杀死一只无辜的动物？
Who would kill an innocent animal?
哈罗德觉得我疯了
Harold thinks I'm crazy,
但我可以发誓 那个镜头里是一个年轻的女人
but I could have sworn that it was young woman in that footage.
- 我会寄给你的  - 是 啊
- I'll send it to you. - Yeah.
但是告诉艾玛祝贺舞蹈队队长
But... tell Emma congratulations on back-up Dance Team Captain.
斯蒂芬说她对此很甜蜜
Steph said she was very sweet about it.
我会让她知道的
I will let her know.
斯蒂芬！
Steph!
快来找护士！我的天！
Someone get the nurse! My god!
拨打911！她需要吃药
Call 911! She needs her meds.
- 斯蒂芬妮！ - 我的天！
- Stephanie! - My god!
- 这非常令人失望  - 是什么？
- This is very disappointing. - What is?
你继续骚扰艾玛·格罗斯曼
Your continued harassment of Emma Grossman.
我们不容忍学校的暴力行为
We don't condone violence at the school.
好吧 听着 这不是我的错
Okay, listen, it was not my fault.
- 我只是… - 斯蒂芬妮·洛福德癫痫发作了
- I was just... - Stephanie Lowford's had a seizure.
她的咪达唑仑不见了 我打了911 他们正在赶来
Her midazolam is missing. I've called 911 and they're on their way.
艾玛
Emma...
我的天
My god.
- 瑞秋 我… - 学校发生了什么事！
- Rachel, I... - Something happened at the school!
你做了什么？
What have you done?
没有什么
Nothing.
- 你不会对我撒谎吧？ - 不 我永远不会
- You wouldn't lie to me, would you? - No. I would never.
我没生气 艾玛 我不是 我只需要知道真相
I'm not mad, Emma. I'm not. I just need to know the truth.
- 关于？ - 每件事
- About? - Everything.
你对你的朋友斯蒂芬妮做了什么吗？
Did you do something to your friend, Stephanie?
她癫痫发作了 这怎么可能是我的错？
She had a seizure. How could that have been my fault?
- 她的狗？ - 那不是我
- Her dog? - That wasn't me.
艾玛 我看见你了 我在环形门摄像头上看到你了
Emma, I saw you. I saw you on the ring-door cam.
- 不 你没有！ - 是的 艾玛 这是你的毛衣
- No, you didn't! - I did, Emma. This is your sweater.
- 不 别骗我了！ - 告诉我真相！
- No. Stop lying to me! - Tell me the truth!
- 艾玛 告诉我！ - 好吧 对不起！
- Emma, tell me! - Okay, I'm sorry!
好吧我让她的狗出来了 好吗？
All right? I let her dog out, okay?
我很想当舞蹈队长 斯蒂芬妮 她只是
I wanted to be Dance Captain so bad, and Stephanie, she just...
她让我很生气
she makes me so angry.
所以我只是   我想
So I just... I thought...
我想伤害她 我把她的狗放了出来
I wanted to hurt her and I let her dog out.
我以为它会回来 我以为他们会找到的 对不起！
I thought it was going to come back. I thought they would find it. I'm sorry!
我保证！我保证我没有伤害它！我发誓！
I promise! I promise I didn't hurt it! I swear!
好的 好的 可以没关系
Okay, okay. Okay. It's okay.
上帝没关系
God. It's okay.
安吉拉阿姨 你能给我一篮子拥抱吗？
What would you give me for a basket of hugs, Aunt Angela?
那里
There.
现在 看到了吗？这没那么糟
Now, see? This isn't so bad.
有点冷
A little cold.
57度
It's 57 degrees.
新鲜空气能增强免疫系统
Fresh air builds the immune system.
你知道 在俄罗斯 他们曾经把孩子捆绑在一起
You know, in Russia, they used to bundle up children
让他们在冬天的雪地里小睡一会儿 真实的故事
and have them take a nap in the snow in the winter. True story.
你想知道古巴人对俄罗斯人的看法吗？
Do you want to know what Cubans think of the Russians?
我勒个去？
What the hell?
什么
What?
太棒了
Great.
- 我需要帮忙  - 当然
- I need a favor. - Of course.
你能过一会儿把他带回来吗？
Can you bring him back inside in a little while?
我有一个小灾难要处理
I have a minor disaster to deal with.
- 别担心 我明白了 - 好的
- Don't worry. I got it. - Okay.
- 一切都好吗？ - 是的 很好 我已经处理好了
- Everything okay? - Yeah, it's good. I've got it handled.
嘿
Hey.
是的 嗨 内森 我是艾玛
Yeah, hi, Nathan. It's Emma.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
不 我什么都没做
No, I'm not doing anything.
是的 我很好 外面很冷
Yeah, I'm good. It's quite chilly out.
艾玛？
Emma?
我想进去热身 吃药
I want to get inside and warm up, take my meds.
- 你能帮我进去吗？ - 无论什么
- Can you help me in there? - Whatever.
艾玛！
Emma!
是的 不 没什么
Yeah, no, it's nothing.
艾玛！
Emma!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
这是我听过的最愚蠢的笑话
That's the stupidest joke I've ever heard.
- 是的  - 上帝
- Yeah. - God.
是 啊
Yeah...
罗伯特？上帝的名义是什么？
Robert? What in God's name?
- 罗伯特 你在干什么？ - 这里发生了什么？
- Robert, what are you doing? - What is happening here?
- 你不理我 我想… - 对不起 我刚打完电话
- You're ignoring me. I'm trying to... - I was finishing a call, I'm sorry.
我可以自己做 看见
I can do it myself. See?
她回来接你
She was coming back to get you.
你不能再等几分钟吗？
You couldn't have waited a few more minutes?
- 让我进去  - 好吧
- Just get me inside. - All right.
那么…他叫什么名字？
So... what's his name?
内森
Nathan.
Nathan...
好吧 我希望他没有这个那么固执
Well, I hope he's not as stubborn as this one.
很抱歉这是剩菜 安吉拉一整天都在医院
Sorry. It's leftovers. Angela's been at the hospital all day.
我已经喂过凯德了
I already fed Cade.
我希望你早些时候没有生气
I hope you're not mad about earlier.
你愚弄了那么多人
You fool so many.
但不是我
But not me.
不再是了
Not anymore.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我记得一切 我知道是你干的
I remember everything. I know it was you.
- 你打算怎么办？ - 这就是我要做的
- What are you gonna do about it? - This is what I'm going to do.
我爱我的妻子 她也爱你
I love my wife, and she loves you,
所以伤害你会伤害她 我不想这样
so hurting you hurts her, and I don't want that.
在她哥哥发生了什么事之后就没有了
Not after what happened to her brother.
所以 我会变得更好
So, I am going to get better...
我什么也不说
and I'm not going to say anything.
以换取什么？
In exchange for what?
你将去寄宿学校 让孩子和我们独处
You will go to boarding school and leave the baby and us alone.
如果我不想做这两件事呢？
What if I don't want to do either of those things?
好吧 那我就说实话
Well, then I'm going to tell the truth.
安吉拉会受到伤害 但你会受到更多的伤害
And Angela will be hurt, but you will be hurt way more.
没有常春藤联盟
No Ivy League.
没有幸福的生活 什么都没有
No happy life. No nothing.
你将永远被锁在外面 完全孤独
You will be locked away forever. Completely alone.
妥协？
Comprende?
蒂奥 整个克拉克
Tio, entiendo claramente.
对话的问题
Que bueno que tuvimos esta conversación.
米吉塔 这是一个奇迹
Te tengo en la mira, mijita.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 这是给谁的？ - 这是给你的 陪伴你
- Who's that for? - It's for you. To keep you company.
- 注意你  - 你要去哪里？
- Keep an eye on you. - Where are you going?
我要去拜访一位老朋友
I'm going to visit an old family friend.
应该几个小时后回来 好吗？
Should be back in a couple of hours, okay?
- 好的 凯德呢？ - 我要带着他
- Okay. What about Cade? - I'm taking him with me.
- 别担心 我很快就回来  - 没关系 你走吧
- Don't worry. I'll be back soon. - That's fine. You go.
- 尽情享受吧  - 可以
- Enjoy yourself. - Okay.
- 臀部怎么样？ - 它还在那里
- How's that hip? - It's still there.
- 它会痊愈的  - 可以
- It'll heal. - Okay.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
你准备好去兜风了吗？
You ready to go for a car ride?
好吧 你会一直睡下去 对吧？
Okay, you're going to sleep the whole way, right?
好了 好孩子
There we go. Good boy.
好了 我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
布莱恩 你好
Brian. Hi.
非常感谢
Thank you.
- 开车怎么样？ - 不错
- How was the drive? - Not bad.
自从…之后 我就再也没有离开过这里
I haven't been out this way since...
嗯 你知道
Well, you know.
我很高兴你伸出援手
I'm glad you reached out.
我一直   也想联系你 只是
I've been... wanting to reach out to you, too, it's just...
我还没鼓起勇气给你打电话
I haven't been able to work up the nerve to call you.
这是
It's...
它一直在吃我…发生了什么
It's been eating at me... what happened,
我必须做的
what I had to do.
停在那里 大卫！我不会让你伤害那个女孩
Stop right there, David! I will not let you hurt that girl.
我也想继续前进 你走开
I want to move on, too. You ask away.
- 任何你需要知道的  - 我哥哥
- Anything you need to know. - My brother.
当他第一次来的时候 和艾玛
When he first arrived, with Emma...
他说了什么？
what did he say?
我是说 他是怎么表现的？他
I mean, how did he act? Did he...
- 他看起来疯了吗？ - 他看起来很稳重 不疯狂
- Did he seem crazy? - He seemed steady. Not crazy.
我想只是难过
Just sad, I guess.
但很明显 他很崇拜那个小女孩
But it was clear as day that he adored that little girl.
顺便问一下 她怎么样？艾玛怎么样？
And how is she, by the way? How's Emma?
她不再那么小了
She's not so little anymore.
真遗憾发生了什么事
It's a shame what happened.
- 我很抱歉  - 不 不 请不要
- And I am so sorry. - No, no, please, don't.
我知道他在威胁她
I know that he was threatening her,
我知道你想保护她
and I know that you were trying to protect her,
那么 拜托 他对你说了什么吗？
so, please, did he say anything to you?
在事情发生之前？在你之前   必须射杀他？
Before it happened? Before you... had to shoot him?
他显然身体不适
He was obviously unwell.
- 但是… - 但是
- But... - But?
有一件事很突出
One thing that stood out...
他说的话我永远不会忘记
something he said I'll never be able to forget.
什么
What?
他说
He said...
“她有点问题 我需要保护她免受自己的伤害 ”
"There's something wrong with her. I need to protect her from herself."
就这样
And that's it.
如果我告诉你 他也说她会再做一次
What if I told you he also said that she would do it again.
你知道这可能意味着什么吗？
Do you know what that might mean?
不
No.
艾玛 你在这里干什么？
Emma, what are you doing here?
只是看看你 确保你仍在呼吸
Just checking on you. Making sure you're still breathing.
- 这很可爱  - 别管它
- This is cute. - Leave it alone.
艾玛 你听到雷声了吗？
Emma, did you hear that thunder?
- 好像暴风雨要来了  - 听起来像是个末日
- It seems like a storm is coming in. - Sounds like a doozy.
你出发前有什么我可以帮你的吗？
Is there anything I can help you with before you head out?
不 我不这么认为 我只是想在暴风雨来临之前离开
No, I don't think so. I just want to get out before the storm hits.
是 啊但谢谢你
Yeah. But thank you.
- 不客气  - 好的 亲爱的
- You're welcome. - Okay, honey.
你够暖和吗？是的 好的 所以
Are you warm enough? Yeah, okay, so...
- 小心  - 好吧再见
- Take care. - All right. Bye.
可以
Okay.
再见 艾玛！我要走了
Bye, Emma! I'm leaving.
接电话
Answer the phone.
- 你想要什么 艾玛？ - 嗨 凯特 我没想到你会接电话
- What do you want, Emma? - Hi, Kat. I didn't think you'd pick up.
嗯 我做到了
Well, I did.
来吧 科拉 拿起 拿起
Come on, Cora. Pick up, pick up.
我只是想找个人谈谈
I just kind of need someone to talk to.
你觉得你能过来吗？
Do you think you could come over?
是的 我只是
Yeah, I just...
我不知道
I don't know...
我真的是个好人   在内心深处
I really am a good person... deep down.
- 好的… - 我就是不能这样下去
- Okay... - I just can't go on like this.
如果你过来 我保证我会告诉你一切
If you come over, I promise I'll tell you everything.
- 一切？ - 每件事
- Everything? - Everything.
请我只是
Please? I just...
我厌倦了一个人
I'm so tired of being alone.
另外
And plus...
我真的需要谈谈内森
I really need to talk about Nathan.
我真的很喜欢他 我不知道该怎么办
I really like him, and I don't know what to do about it.
也许你可以给我建议什么的
Maybe you could just give me advice or something.
- 好吗？ - 好的 艾玛
- All right? - Okay, Emma.
但前提是你把一切都告诉我
But only if you tell me everything.
真正地
Really?
是的 我真的邀请凯特过来试着让空气清新一点
Yeah, I actually invited Kat over to try and clear the air a little bit.
- 我认为这很好 是的  - 是 啊
- I think that's great, yeah. - Yeah.
不过她不应该待太久
She shouldn't stay too long, though,
也许你能在一个小时左右过来？
so maybe you can come over in, like, an hour or so?
真正地那太酷了 可以是 啊
Really? That would be cool. Okay. Yeah.
是 啊不过 她可能随时都会来 所以我得让你走了
Yeah. She'll probably be here any minute, though, so I got to let you go.
- 好的  - 好吧
- Okay. - All right.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
嘿进来吧 笨蛋
Hey. Come in, silly.
我给我们做了热巧克力 就像我爸爸以前做的那样
I made us hot chocolate. Just like my dad used to make.
怎么样？
How is it?
很好 我想
Good, I guess.
内森怎么了？这就是你想说的吗 艾玛？
What's up with Nathan? Is that what you want to talk about, Emma?
我只是
I just...
我从来都不知道如何在他身边行动
I never really know how to act around him.
如果你喜欢他 就做你自己
Well, if you like him, just be yourself.
有人和我聊天真的很好
It's really nice to have someone to talk to.
我从来没有真正的人可以交谈
I never really have anyone to talk to.
- 不是真的  - 也许这是有原因的
- Not really. - Maybe there's a reason for that.
很难与众不同 你知道吗？
It's hard to be different, you know?
最近事情有点疯狂
Things have been kind of crazy lately.
- 怎么会这样？ - 我叔叔
- How so? - My uncle...
我的继父
My step-uncle...
他想把我送到寄宿学校
he wanted to send me away to a boarding school.
他以为我要对孩子做点什么
He thought I was going to do something to the baby.
是吗？
Did you?
- 孩子很好  - 你叔叔不是
- The baby's fine. - Your uncle isn't.
每一个动作都有一个相等和相反的反应
Every action has an equal and opposite reaction.
牛顿第三定律 这是基础物理学
Newton's Third Law. That's basic physics.
意外发生
Accidents happen.
来吧快点
Come on! Hurry up.
快点
Hurry up!
- 斯蒂芬？意外？ - 确切地
- Steph? An accident? - Exactly.
她的狗呢？
And her dog?
那太悲惨了
That was so tragic.
米洛和埃利斯夫人呢？你爸爸艾玛呢？
And Milo and Mrs. Ellis? And your dad, Emma?
- 你自己的爸爸？ - 他开始了
- Your own dad? - He started it.
- 如何？ - 热巧克力
- How? - Hot chocolate.
顺便问一下 情况如何？
How was it by the way?
不要洒在我的地毯上
Don't spill on my rug.
就在那里
There it is.
花了这么长时间 我想这可能行不通
It was taking so long, I thought it might not work.
你给了我什么？
What did you give me?
每件事字面上
Everything. Literally.
- 你逃不了… - 逃避这个？
- You won't get away with... - Get away with this?
你太夸张了
You're so melodramatic.
你想看点酷的吗？
You wanna see something cool?
-  911. 你有什么紧急情况？ - 我的上帝 请帮帮我！
- 911. What's your emergency? - My god, please help me!
我叫艾玛·格罗斯曼！有个女孩   她疯了！
My name is Emma Grossman! There's this girl... she's insane!
我邀请她过来吃热巧克力 结果她生起了火！
I invited her over to come and have hot chocolate and she started a fire!
她在攻击我！请帮帮我！
She's attacking me! Please help me!
那是我逃避的声音
That was the sound of me getting away with it.
每次都有效
Works every time.
我是个疯子
I'm a psycho.
说起来很有趣
That's fun to say.
可惜没人会听到
Too bad no one will ever hear that.
莱瓦夫人 米洛 埃利斯夫人
Mrs. Leyva. Milo. Mrs. Ellis.
克洛伊 我爸爸
Chloe. My dad.
斯蒂芬妮和那只可笑的狗
Stephanie and that ridiculous dog.
你罗伯特叔叔
You. Uncle Robert.
你们这些家伙都惹了太多麻烦
You guys all just cause too much trouble.
别惹精神病
Don't mess with psychos.
真正地
Really...
我刚才说了什么？
What did I just say?
我是说 你想用这个做什么？
I mean, what are you trying to do with this?
上帝
God.
- 现在你打算做什么？哭？ - 请
- Now what are you going to do? Cry? - Please.
- 你不必这么做  - 你已经睡了 好吧
- You don't have to do this. - Just go to sleep already. All right?
我不想这么说 但这有点无聊了
I hate to say it, but this is getting a little boring.
谢谢你对内森的建议 做我自己
Thank you for the advice about Nathan. Just be myself.
我会尝试的
I'll try.
没有你 这是不可能的
This wouldn't have been possible without you.
你真的是我最好的朋友
You really are the best friend I've ever had.
艾玛
Emma...
艾玛？
Emma?
安吉拉 你在家吗？
Angela, are you home?
你好
Hello?
安吉拉？
Angela?
艾玛？
Emma?
我来了 伙计！
I'm coming, buddy!
爸爸来了
Daddy's coming.
是 啊我来了 伙计
Yeah. Here I come, buddy.
艾玛？
Emma?
凯德！
Cade!
爸爸来了 伙计
Daddy's coming, buddy.
我来了 伙计 爸爸来了
I'm coming, buddy. Daddy's here.
一切都很好
Everything's okay.
艾玛？
Emma?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
相等和相反的反应
Equal and opposite reactions.
老实说 它可能总是以这种方式结束
To be honest, it was probably always going to end up this way.
对不起 罗伯特
I am sorry, Robert.
某种程度上
Sort of.
安吉拉
Angela.
艾玛！
Emma!
- 安吉拉阿姨！ - 艾玛！你做了什么？
- Aunt Angela! - Emma! What did you do?
- 什么？ - 他对你的评价是对的！
- What? - He was right about you!
- 你在说什么？ - 你爸爸
- What are you talking about? - Your dad.
我哥哥 他爱你胜过一切 但他是对的！
My brother, he loved you more than anything, but he was right!
你是个怪物！
You're a monster!
你不是那个意思！凯特只是想杀了我们！
You don't mean that! Kat just tried to kill us!
说谎者！你对她做了什么？
Liar! What did you do to her?
给罗伯特？你做了什么 艾玛？
To Robert? What did you do, Emma?
安吉拉！
Angela!
不……不要走
No... don't go.
罗伯特！
Robert!
嗨 朋友
Hi, friend.
罗伯特！
Robert!
罗伯特 醒醒 罗伯特 醒醒吧！
Robert, wake up. Robert, wake up, please!
快点 快点 起来！
Come on. Come on, get up!
快点 我们得把你弄出去！
Come on, we've got to get you out of here!
来吧 罗伯特 请
Come on, Robert. Please!
帮助请
Help! Please!
请我阿姨！她还在里面！
Please! My aunt! She's still in there!
这个女孩   她试图烧毁我们的房子
This girl... she tried to burn our house down.
- 求你了！你必须设法救她！ - 你在这里等着！
- Please! You've got to try and save her! - You wait here!
艾玛！你没事吧？
Emma! Are you okay?
- 我的天  - 耶稣基督
- My god. - Jesus Christ.
没关系 没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
这到底是怎么发生的？
How the hell did this happen?
没关系 没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
那么现在会发生什么呢？
So what's going to happen now?
我们有一个了不起的女人可以收留你
We have an amazing woman who can take you in
直到一切都整理好
until everything gets sorted.
我很抱歉 艾玛
I'm so sorry, Emma.
我无法想象这对你来说有多困难
I can't imagine how difficult this is for you.
我爱我的阿姨
I loved my aunt.
还有我叔叔
And my uncle.
凯德和我至少能在一起吗？
Can Cade and I at least stay together?
我们会尽力的
We'll do our best.
他是我唯一剩下的家人
He's the only family I have left.
我需要打几个电话
I need to make a few calls.
你需要什么吗？
Is there anything you need?
艾玛 你知道这不是你的错
Emma, you know this isn't your fault.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
我们是格罗斯曼 我们高高在上
We're Grossmans. We rise above.
可以
Okay.